[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fastest ocean animal?", "correct_answer": "Sailfish", "incorrect_answers": ["Swordfish", "Marlin", "Wahoo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After Indiana Jones steals the Ark from the Germans, which two modes of transportation are used to get the Ark to the secret base in the Greek Islands?", "correct_answer": "Steamer ship and submarine", "incorrect_answers": ["Train and submarine", "Steamer ship and railroad", "Submarine and transport aircraft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following drugs thins the blood?  (That is, it decreases the ability of the blood to clot.)", "correct_answer": "Coumadin (warfarin)", "incorrect_answers": ["hydrochlorothiazide", "Lexapro (escitalopram)", "Biaxin (clarithromycin)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The North American Beaver is Canadas National symbol that adorns which Canadian coin?", "correct_answer": "Nickle", "incorrect_answers": ["Penny", "Quarter", "Dime"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Cars, Rust-eze was McQueens major sponsor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these ways of defence and attack do ants use?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Injecting or spraying chemicals", "Stinging", "Biting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the word \u201cmantis\u201d mean?", "correct_answer": "Prophet or fortuneteller", "incorrect_answers": ["Savage insect", "Killer or hunter", "Leaflike"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture for 1980?", "correct_answer": "Cant Stop the Music", "incorrect_answers": ["Friday the 13th", "Xanadu", "The Nude Bomb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The story of Salvador Dali and his wife is the subject of this 2009 movie.", "correct_answer": "Little Ashes", "incorrect_answers": ["Dali  I: The Surreal Story", "Salvador and Gala:The Surreal Life", "Just Dali and Me"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Chonmage is a mans hairstyle traditional for this country.", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Korea", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Star Wars: A New Hope, who was R2-D2 and C-3POs original master?", "correct_answer": "Princess Leia", "incorrect_answers": ["Obi Wan Kenobi", "Luke Skywalker", "Anakin Skywalker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are 12 astronomical constellations.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]